# NAZRIN NOORZAN

WEB DEVELOPER



# **PROFILE**

Currently working for almost 3 years as a solo web developer at Cause Effect, a digital performance agency. Mostly building websites through WordPress and Shopify. High interest slightly towards front-end development.

I'm a self-taught developer. Having knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, Liquid, MySQL, SEO and Git. Currently, in learning of React. I am a kind of guy that pretty independence and love challenges.

# **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Software Engineering** 

University of East London (UEL)

2014 - 2016

Diploma in Computer Engineering

Universiti Malaysia Perlis (UniMAP)

2011 - 2014

## FOLLOW



Facebook / nazrin.noorzan



Instagram / nazrinnoorzan



Sungai Besi, Kuala Lumpur



017-437 3460



nzrink1@gmail.com



/nazrin-noorzan

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### WEB DEVELOPER

Cause Effect / Kuala Lumpur / 2018 - Present

- Developing websites for clients including website tracking and SEO.
- Troubleshoot any website, email or server issue for clients.
- Highest Achievement: Created a tournament registration form for Free Fire game with further player in-game data validation using an API provided by Garena.

#### HELPDESK AND IT SUPPORT

Rhino Alliance Sdn Bhd / Kuala Lumpur / 2016 - 2018

- Testing software patches for KTMB Token Vending Machine before going live to public.
- Coordinate & manage on-field technicians so that the task is done within SLA.
- Highest Achievement : Managed to solve minor database issue without going to the database admin.

#### COMPUTER TECHNICIAN

Scrap Computer Trading Sdn Bhd / Shah Alam, Selangor / 2013 - 2014

- Troubleshoot PC hardware based on the problems that customers describe.
- Highest Achievement: Managed to install air cleaning gun system at the premise for ease of cleaning scrap PC.

# **SKILLS & EXPERTIZE**

HTML	_	Creativity	_
CSS		Flexibility	_
JavaScript		Work in group	-
PHP		Personality	_
WordPress	_	Photoshop	
Shopify		Adobe XD	_

# **HOBBY AND INTERESTS**





Futsal





Music Movie